<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blue Jay</title>
    <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blue Jay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 22:59:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://jayjhan8.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Read a Book</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/i-read-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 22:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/i-read-a-book/</guid>
      <description>I have one week left until I go back for my 2nd round of chemo. While I&amp;rsquo;m dreading the time I get to be stuck on the same floor of the hospital for 5 days in a row, I&amp;rsquo;m also enjoying every moment that I am not there. Spending time with my parents, conversing with friends, and even working from home. Speaking of work, I want to give a shoutout to my co-workers and the executive staff for supporting me in my fight against cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Back Home</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/back-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 17:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/back-home/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m finally back home. It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 days, and boy am I glad to be back. I&amp;rsquo;m much better now than when I got discharged. With all the poison fully loaded into my body, I felt like I had an out-of-body experience for most of the first day out of the hospital. It&amp;rsquo;s almost felt like a fever except you don&amp;rsquo;t feel weak. Your mind is constantly battling another conscience trying to take over and your body responds in all sorts of ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1, Day 1 - 3</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/week-1-day-1---3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 09:30:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/week-1-day-1---3/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 I got admitted around 11AM, but the actual chemo didn&amp;rsquo;t start until 7PM. I drew more blood, added a PICC line (a glorified IV), and got a MRI done on my brain just to make sure there is no cancer there. Today is my first day after the 6 full hours of chemo that started around 7PM yesterday and ended around 2AM the following day. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really do much because I was so anxious in anticipating what the chemo will do to my body on the first day.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VIP</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/vip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 21:34:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/vip/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow is the day! I will get admitted around 11AM and I imagine the nurses will work their magic in hooking me up to all the drugs that I need ;). The names of these drugs form my chemotherapy regimen called VIP. I knew I was special, just thought I&amp;rsquo;d never hear it from a doctor. Nurses have informed me of my potential side effects and what to expect for my treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post!</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 14:19:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome everyone. Thanks for stopping by my blog. This is very new to me, so I&amp;rsquo;m not quite sure what to write now. I decided to try something new given the recent turn of events in my life. As many of you know, I was recently diagnosed with stage 3 testicular cancer. Before you get so wrapped up about the word &amp;ldquo;cancer,&amp;rdquo; let me tell you how it all happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
