<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blue Jay</title>
    <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blue Jay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 12:49:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://jayjhan8.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 12:49:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/sun/</guid>
      <description>Seattle is one of the most beautiful places to live in. It took me a while to get used to the winter drag, but I&amp;rsquo;ve adapted and learned to appreciate the summer. The sun&amp;rsquo;s out today, birds are chirping, and the bees are zapping away &amp;ndash; summer&amp;rsquo;s just around the corner. On my rooftop, I can look far out into the horizon to the South, where there are so many trees and other plants interspersed around buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick update</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/quick-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 19:09:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/quick-update/</guid>
      <description>I realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t speak about couple big events coming up. I have finished 2 rounds of chemo and I&amp;rsquo;m currently on my last off week before I head back into the hospital. This coming Thursday, I have my 2nd CT scan. This is the first since I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten chemo, so we&amp;rsquo;ll have a good comparison of before and after chemo. Although I won&amp;rsquo;t know much about it that day, I continually ask for your thoughts and prayers that the cancer is full eradicated.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Did you notice?</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/did-you-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 22:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/did-you-notice/</guid>
      <description>You may notice that the blog looks slightly different, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t, scroll down. You can now comment on each of my post. I have gotten many requests to get this comment feature implemented, so I hope it works as intended. When I was talking to Sammy earlier, I realized that the audience of my blog has grown pretty quickly. I realize that the point of this blog is for me to tell my story to you, but I figured it&amp;rsquo;d be nice to hear from you and be more engaging than just my words on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 20:43:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/week-2/</guid>
      <description>Nausea is much worse this time around. I even asked for some additional anti-nausea meds because I can&amp;rsquo;t stop thinking about it. Aside from the nausea, everything else is what I have expected so far &amp;ndash; fatigue, loss of apetite, constipation, and fluid build-up near my head. I thought that this round might be easier knowing what to expect, but it&amp;rsquo;s.. still difficult. I&amp;rsquo;m currently on my 3rd day of chemo this week, and I&amp;rsquo;m dreading the last few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Round Two</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/round-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 22:41:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/round-two/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the next round of chemo. I am loving my new almost-bald look, and I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty normal aside from a few cold symptoms. Alot has happened these past 3 weeks. I have felt the worst of chemo within the first week, and then I felt better and better each day. I thought I was going to go on with my normal life for a week, but I began to cough and sneeze more frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 10:45:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/friends/</guid>
      <description>Friend
/frend/
noun
Old English frēond, of Germanic origin; related to Dutch vriend and German Freund, from an Indo-European root meaning ‘to love&amp;rsquo;
 This blog was partly for me so that I can write and process my own thoughts. But this blog was primarily written for you. For my friends, family, and anyone who cares enough to take the time out of their day to read this thing. It&amp;rsquo;s been about 2 1&amp;frasl;2 weeks since the first day of treatment, and I still wonder if this is all just a bad dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Read a Book</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/i-read-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 22:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/i-read-a-book/</guid>
      <description>I have one week left until I go back for my 2nd round of chemo. While I&amp;rsquo;m dreading the time I get to be stuck on the same floor of the hospital for 5 days in a row, I&amp;rsquo;m also enjoying every moment that I am not there. Spending time with my parents, conversing with friends, and even working from home. Speaking of work, I want to give a shoutout to my co-workers and the executive staff for supporting me in my fight against cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Back Home</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/back-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 17:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/back-home/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m finally back home. It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 days, and boy am I glad to be back. I&amp;rsquo;m much better now than when I got discharged. With all the poison fully loaded into my body, I felt like I had an out-of-body experience for most of the first day out of the hospital. It&amp;rsquo;s almost felt like a fever except you don&amp;rsquo;t feel weak. Your mind is constantly battling another conscience trying to take over and your body responds in all sorts of ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1, Day 1 - 3</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/week-1-day-1---3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 09:30:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/week-1-day-1---3/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 I got admitted around 11AM, but the actual chemo didn&amp;rsquo;t start until 7PM. I drew more blood, added a PICC line (a glorified IV), and got a MRI done on my brain just to make sure there is no cancer there. Today is my first day after the 6 full hours of chemo that started around 7PM yesterday and ended around 2AM the following day. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really do much because I was so anxious in anticipating what the chemo will do to my body on the first day.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VIP</title>
      <link>https://jayjhan8.github.io/vip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 21:34:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jayjhan8.github.io/vip/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow is the day! I will get admitted around 11AM and I imagine the nurses will work their magic in hooking me up to all the drugs that I need ;). The names of these drugs form my chemotherapy regimen called VIP. I knew I was special, just thought I&amp;rsquo;d never hear it from a doctor. Nurses have informed me of my potential side effects and what to expect for my treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
